ZACK MERRELL

DIGITAL ARTIST ♥ SANTA CRUZ, 95060, UNITED STATES **\((831)**566-6437

• DETAILS •

204 HEATH ST, SANTA CRUZ, 95060, United States (831)566-6437 zmerrell831@gmail.com

• LINKS •

My Online Portfolio

• SKILLS •

Digital Illustration using Adobe Creative Cloud Suite

HTML and CSS

Photography

3D Modeling

JavaScript Coding

Video Production

HOBBIES

Skateboarding Soccer

PROFILE

I want to bring my knowledge in the Adobe Creative Cloud Suite, as well as other programs ranging from coding in Atom to 3D models in Maya or Dimension, to the workplace and utilize my experience to achieve both my own goals, as well as the goals of my employers and coworkers in the workplace. I want to do everything possible to create.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Freelance Art/Design

November 2014 — Present

- Designed and created multiple logos for start-up businesses and professional social media accounts
- Sold prints of personal projects made in the Adobe Creative Cloud Suite to multiple people
- Designed a variety of posters for different needs, causes, and people

Sales Associate at Vans, San Jose

November 2018 — August 2020

- Helped numerous customers find the apparel that was right for them
- Inspired outfits for customers looking for a wardrobe overhaul
- Designed multiple custom pairs of shoes for customers looking for something more personal to them

Shop Help at Northwest Signs, Santa Cruz

August 2020 — Present

• Hands-on, builder of signs for multiple businesses (Ex. O'Neil Surf Shop)

EDUCATION

Digital Media, San Jose State University, San

Jose August 2017 — May 2022

- · Learned to create using a variety of software
- Expanding my skills in digital illustration, design, coding, 3D modeling, photography and many more

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

D1 Club Soccer at San Jose State University

August 2017 — Spring 2020

- Goalkeeper
- · Captain of the team

Nu Alpha Kappa Fraternity

Joined February 2020

- Actively held positions on the Executive Board (February 2020-May 2022)
- Created all of the design work for the those two years

25+ Hours of Community Service

• Beach clean-ups, Homeless shelter help, etc.